{
    "subject": "resource/Urapopstar",
    "predicate": "property/modes",
    "object": "resource/Multiplayer_game",
    "human_readable": "Urapopstar is played in multiplayer mode.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8957921266555786,
            "question": "Does Urapopstar require internet connectivity for multiplayer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8918635249137878,
            "question": "Are there different teams in multiplayer Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8762551546096802,
            "question": "Can players communicate with each other during a multiplayer Urapopstar game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8713102340698242,
            "question": "What kind of interaction is involved in multiplayer Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.858795702457428,
            "question": "Is there a competitive element to multiplayer Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7921186685562134,
            "question": "What is the primary mode of play in Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6166985630989075,
            "question": "Can Urapopstar be played with multiple people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.489856481552124,
            "question": "Is Urapopstar a single-player game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45923247933387756,
            "question": "Does Urapopstar offer any cooperative gameplay options?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36782267689704895,
            "question": "How many players can participate in a game of Urapopstar?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Urapopstar is played in multiplayer mode.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9067_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Urapopstar offer any cooperative gameplay options?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9067_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Urapopstar a single-player game?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9067_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can Urapopstar be played with multiple people?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9067_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9067_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9067_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9067_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9067_4.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe text mentions that \"Urapopstar is a multiplayer browser-based role-playing game\" which suggests that it is indeed played in multiplayer mode."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Urapopstar, describing it as a \"multiplayer browser-based role-playing game,\" which supports the statement that Urapopstar is played in multiplayer mode."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}